{
  "id": "006-food",
  "title": "Food & Drinks",
  "questions": [
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "vanduo",
      "choices": [
        "water",
        "wine",
        "coffee",
        "beer"
      ],
      "answer": "water",
      "tts": "vanduo"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "kava",
      "choices": [
        "coffee",
        "tea",
        "beer",
        "milk"
      ],
      "answer": "coffee",
      "tts": "kava"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "arbata",
      "choices": [
        "tea",
        "coffee",
        "juice",
        "water"
      ],
      "answer": "tea",
      "tts": "arbata"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "alus",
      "choices": [
        "beer",
        "wine",
        "juice",
        "milk"
      ],
      "answer": "beer",
      "tts": "alus"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "vynas",
      "choices": [
        "wine",
        "beer",
        "water",
        "tea"
      ],
      "answer": "wine",
      "tts": "vynas"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "",
      "choices": [],
      "tts": "vanduo"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "",
      "choices": [],
      "tts": "kava"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "",
      "choices": [],
      "tts": "arbata"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "",
      "choices": [],
      "tts": "alus"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "",
      "choices": [],
      "tts": "vynas"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "duona",
      "choices": [
        "bread",
        "meat",
        "cheese",
        "fish"
      ],
      "answer": "bread",
      "tts": "duona"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "sūris",
      "choices": [
        "cheese",
        "meat",
        "fish",
        "bread"
      ],
      "answer": "cheese",
      "tts": "sūris"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "mėsa",
      "choices": [
        "meat",
        "fish",
        "cheese",
        "bread"
      ],
      "answer": "meat",
      "tts": "mėsa"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "žuvis",
      "choices": [
        "fish",
        "meat",
        "cheese",
        "bread"
      ],
      "answer": "fish",
      "tts": "žuvis"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "",
      "choices": [],
      "tts": "duona"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "",
      "choices": [],
      "tts": "sūris"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "",
      "choices": [],
      "tts": "mėsa"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "",
      "choices": [],
      "tts": "žuvis"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "skanu",
      "choices": [
        "tasty",
        "bad",
        "hot",
        "cold"
      ],
      "answer": "tasty",
      "tts": "skanu"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "",
      "choices": [],
      "tts": "skanu"
    }
  ]
}